The truth is dead.
The truth has died
and turned this house into a graveyard.
The truth is dead.
Good Morning, Ap…
Appa.
Appa?
Lavana sir!
Hello?
Doctor is on his morning rounds.
He can't talk right now.
Open your mouth once, please.
Ma'am?
- How are you feeling now?
- Better, sir.
Good! You are doing very well.
You have nothing to worry about.
Just wait and watch.
You'll be up and home in 2 days.
She totally bought that lie, doctor.
She thinks she'll live to 100 now.
A lie is like a sweet melody.
It's music to the ears.
A sweet lie is better than
a troubling truth, junior.
A doctor's job is to offer relief.
Not to cause more pain.
She has only four days left to live.
Call her son in an hour
and ask him to take her home.
Let us see this ward.
Doctor!
Doctor, there's a phone call for you.
Not when I'm with the patients.
Don't you know?
Note their details.
Tell them I'll call back later.
I did tell them, sir.
But they're saying it's urgent.
Who's in such a hurry?
It's Mr. Lavanappa Raju, sir.
Lavana?
You start examining this ward.
I'll join you.
Junior!
Don't tell them the truth.
It'll scare them.
- Hello?
- Uncle?
- It's Lavana.
- Tell me, Lavana?
You need to come to our house urgently.
Dad wants to discuss
something personal with you.
This early in the morning?
Is your father fine, Lavana?
He fell unconscious again this morning.
It's a miracle he's still alive, sir.
Please don't say that, doctor.
The truth is often harsh, doctor.
I told you a year ago that
he wouldn't live beyond four months.
When he's questioning
35 years of my experience,
what can I do but stay silent?
I haven't seen anyone live this long…
with end-stage liver cancer.
And that too, while still drinking.
I'm insisting on a hospital visit
just to see this super-human.
There's nothing really that I can do.
Why don't you do one thing?
Tell me, doctor.
Try sending him to a rehab
in America to quit alcohol.
I don't know.
He is already a man of miracles.
That will lead to more complications.
You see, Dr. Achari.
He's an alcoholic with
an undiagnosed psychological disorder.
He suffers from
phobias, delusions, and hallucinations.
He uses alcohol to numb these symptoms.
If you try to make him quit now,
won't the withdrawal worsen his symptoms?
What do you suggest then?
First, we need to diagnose
his mental disorder.
Second, is his disorder genetic…
or was it caused by trauma?
This is what we need to figure out.
Then he needs to be on medication
and go through therapy.
In order to do any of this,
you need to first bring him to me, doctor.
BHUVANA'S ESTATE
So, Achchamma? How are you?
Just getting by, sir.
What do you mean "getting by"?
Aren't you keeping well?
Sir's condition has
gotten me worried, sir.
Of course, I'm not fine.
Greetings, sir.
Who's that?
I've never seen her here before.
She's my daughter-in-law, sir.
All the servants quit, one by one.
So, I brought her in for help.
Coming back to the point,
what happened to your Appa?
You know how it is, sir.
It's the same story every night.
The memories of his younger
son are eating him up inside.
That's not all.
He keeps screaming "Kusuma! Kusuma!"
loudly in his sleep.
Has she been out lately?
Go on.
I guess he missed his
son more than usual today.
He cried and cried
until he fell unconscious.
Do you know all this for sure,
or do you just think you do?
Oh, please, sir.
You never believe me.
Why would I make something like that up?
Only you would know that!
- Is he in the room?
- Yeah, he is. Go!
Where else would he be?
"Is he in the room?" he asks.
He's been this way since childhood.
He has never trusted me.
Injustice has prevailed.
The 'Kauravas' have been betrayed.
How can the 'Pandavas' take the throne?
They can't.
They shouldn't.
The heirs of a 'nobody'
have ruled the kingdom.
He wasn't fortunate
enough to have children.
He would die if he tried.
No! No! No! No! No!
A mistake has been made.
You, lady!
Were the Pandavas born to him?
Or you tell me, lady!
Were they his biological sons?
Why don't you answer me?
Were Pandavas really born to him?!
Why won't you believe when I say so?
The Pandavas were not born to him.
- They weren't born to him.
- Hey, Ramudu!
- They weren't! They weren't!
- Ramudu! Don't hit yourself!
Ramudu!
Were the Pandavas born to him?
No, they weren't.
Then why won't they answer me?
Who?
They're not here anymore.
They left because they
don't have an answer for me.
Who is it this time?
It was them. Kunti and Madri.
- And…
- Kunti?
How did you even enter…
when the walls are rotating?
It's not the walls that are rotating.
I came in with them.
I didn't notice you.
It's fine.
You seemed busy with them.
With whom?
With Kunti and Madri.
Is it?
Were they here? Are they here?
Where are they?
- Where are they?
- They feared you and ran away.
Tell me if they come again.
I need to ask some questions.
Alright.
I'll tell you. Sit down calmly first.
Sit.
What's with these creepers and pumpkins?
Didn't I ask you to get these removed?
Don't touch them!
Let them be.
I hoped my second son
would look like a pumpkin too.
Let them grow, at least.
Why did you ask for me?
Me?
I didn't ask you to come.
You didn't?
But Lavana said you wanted
to talk to me personally.
That guy? He always does this.
He blames me for things I don't do.
- He hates me for some reason.
- Yeah, fine.
I came here to talk to you.
Then, why are you silent?
Spill it!
I want you to come and
see the doctor with me.
You are my doctor, right?
Why go to someone else?
- I'm just a general doctor. You…
- Yes, I know, I know.
You'll take me to a cancer doctor
or a mental doctor, right?
Not a mental doctor.
A psychiatrist.
Yeah! Psychiatrist!
Psychiatrist! Psychiatrist!
Some big psychiatrist!
I won't come. I won't come.
He doesn't know anything.
Am I crazy to go there?
I look sane, right?
I'm not coming. No way!
Fine. Don't come!
Don't come.
Consult the cancer doctor at least?
No, I won't come. I won't come.
He doesn't know anything.
It's a waste of money.
A year ago, he told me
I'd die in four months.
I didn't die, did I?
I won't come! I won't come! I won't come!
He doesn't know anything. He doesn't.
- He doesn't know anything.
- Yes, he doesn't know anything.
- Don't get any closer.
- He doesn't know anything.
That's why he's puzzled
you're still alive!
He longs for your holy presence.
You won't die, will you?
But you'll drive us to death instead.
One day at a time.
Sorry, Achari.
I shouldn't have called you and
hurt you like this.
So, you asked me to come?
Yes, didn't Lavana tell you?
He always does this.
I pampered him so much
for being my only son,
- and he turned out so useless.
- Don't go down that road.
Leave it. Tell me why you called
before you forget.
Sit. I'll tell you.
I'm sitting. Tell me.
You're all wondering how
I'm still alive, right?
Yes.
I know why.
What do you know?
I have…
I've been possessed by a demon, Achari.
- Hey! You're speaking nonsense again.
- No, it makes sense.
I'll explain it to you. Sit down once.
Tell me.
Remember "Fill in the Blanks" from school?
I remember.
"Dash" is a deadly demon.
Fill in the blank.
Doubt is a deadly demon.
That's the demon I'm possessed with.
Doubt is a drug.
I won't die till its high wears off.
What are you doubtful about?
He's listening.
Hey!
You little rascal!
I know it's you!
How dare you spy on me
in my own house?
Hey!
Where are you?
Wait, I'll have Achari deal with you.
Who's that?
It's Kusuma, man.
- Kusuma?
- Yes.
Even though my body has given up,
it's doubt that's kept
my soul trapped in a jar.
Please fulfill my last wish and
free me from the curse of this jar.
Did you read this?
They're running blood tests to
identify the biological parents.
You are a doctor, right?
Take my blood and find out
if Kusuma is my son.
Here.
Take it. Take my blood.
Hey! Ramudu!
Ramudu, stop it!
Your blood alone won't do.
We need his too.
How will you get a dead boy's blood?
Ramudu!
What have you turned into, man?
See, you're bleeding!
Why did this doubt even arise?
So, the test is not possible?
Look, Kusuma died eight years ago.
How can we get his blood now?
You promised to fulfill my last wish.
- Yes, but
- Is there no other way?
I'm not sure.
See, DNA testing is a new science.
The world is just discovering it.
Is there no way to test
without his blood?
That's what I've been saying.
I don't know.
But as a doctor who's
studied the human body,
they'd need some sample
from the body, if not blood.
But I can't guarantee anything.
So, stop this nonsense
and come see the doctor.
A psychiatrist can help
eliminate those thoughts.
You may leave now.
How are you?
He's hanging between life and death.
If you stop being stubborn
and talk to him,
it may do him good.
What is it, uncle?
Did my dad scare you?
You seem to have zoned out.
Eat, eat.
What else is happening, Lavana?
I'm applying for an American visa.
- I'll leave once it gets approved.
- Oh.
I remember you telling me.
With all the property you'll inherit,
why would you work
under someone in America?
What's the point of all this inheritance?
She won't talk to me.
I don't understand a thing he says.
Instead of enduring his daily antics,
I'd rather leave.
What if something happens
to him after you leave?
They gave him a year, and so I waited.
Sinners don't die that easily, uncle.
He put my mom through hell.
He doesn't seem to be dying anytime soon.
I've known you since
you were a kid, Lavana.
Will you be hateful of everyone forever?
Growing up, people teased
me for being premature.
Premature babies come with flaws, right?
‘Hateful', he says.
Love doesn't always have
to be on display, like yours is.
There is love in my concern for him.
I love him enough…
to tolerate his torture
while giving medicines.
But lately,
as I watch him struggling to stay alive,
my love makes me want
to put him out of his misery.
I'm running away before I do that.
‘Hateful', he says.
As someone who visits once in a while,
how would you know the pain we go through?
He's confined himself in
his room like a madman.
If I keep worrying about him,
I'll end up the same way.
That's why I'm leaving.
Did he just call me mad?
Who's mad?
He thinks I'm mad?
Saying I confined myself to the room.
The world seems so vast when we're young.
It shrinks as we grow.
We think it's because
we've grown physically.
But the truth is, we've
stopped growing mentally.
I shut myself in my room, eh?
What does he know about it?
Once upon a time, my world was vast too.
If you turned my life into a film,
it would be two parts.
At least two parts!
I was a free bird out there.
Why did you put me in this cage?
Your eyes might've witnessed
many many ups and downs.
This night, o wanderer,
come, see this path.
Any man's life is ruined,
if he doesn't travel
He knowingly
falls in the traps.
The world around
us, filled with norms,
will the hungry soul
stop, even if you try?
If you sprinkle water
in the name of morals,
will this raging thirst calm down?
I will engulf you in waves of beauty.
I will trap you in my embrace.
O explorer of the lands,
will you explore my body?
O universal beauty,
I will dance with you in joy
Rock and roll!
Rock and rock and roll!
Crossing mountains,
valleys and rivers,
climbing many peaks,
didn't it make you even a bit tired?
A horse that wanders in the forest,
a life with hope and spirit,
should it not tread carefully?
If there's no freedom on this land,
does it matter how long we live?
What's the point of stopping
after I learn this truth?
Even a horse that gallops excitedly
has to halt at a beautiful garden,
to drive away his exhaustion and
fulfill his needs.
The world around
us, filled with norms,
will the hungry soul
stop, even if you try?
Even if you hold it in a cage,
will this raging thirst calm down?
I will engulf you in waves of my beauty
I will trap you in my embrace.
O explorer of the lands,
will you explore my body?
O universal beauty,
I will dance with you in joy
- Rock and roll!
Hey, rock and roll!
Rock and rock and roll!
Mogambo Khush Hua!
This is the first chapter of my story.
In this, I'm a tireless traveler,
like an early human.
For five years,
I was an aimless bird with
no attachments whatsoever.
But my first mistake was…
a discussion with this guy.
How did you know I was here?
It took me two months, man.
London to Singapore, then to
Morocco, Switzerland, and France.
My search led me to Brahmanda
Nagaram, and here I am!
Wow, that's one long journey!
You should have visited
Kasi and returned home.
Why did you come here?
Hey.
You're meeting a friend after ages.
Is this how you talk to him?
Oh no!
Forgive me, dear friend!
May I know the true purpose of your visit?
Your father has ordered to
see you at his palace, at once.
I'm no cattle to be dragged back home.
I don't want to return home.
Why do you dislike us so much?
I like you people.
It's your meaningless
traditions that I dislike.
Yeah, like your deeds
are rather meaningful.
Got a glimpse of it last night.
Yeah! What's wrong with that?
A man and a woman dancing in joy.
You haven't changed a bit, Ramappa.
Everyone is awaiting your return.
Why don't you visit once?
Your little tricks to make me
return home haven't changed either.
I told you the world is
my home when I left.
I'm not coming back.
Hence, please save your precious time…
and return to the fort immediately.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Do you remember your dad's face?
Ramudu? Ramudu?
Ramudu!
Appa?
Come in.
Ew! Why is the room so dirty--
That's just how the room is.
Appa is a bit crazy.
He tends to scatter things everywhere.
He won't let us clean it if he comes out.
Let's clean before that. Come.
Wow! A pumpkin!
- Can I take this?
- He'll kill you.
Don't touch a thing, and get over here.
Mother-in-law?
How did he go crazy?
He's got ears like a bat.
He can hear your thoughts too.
I'll tell you later. Get to work.
Appa?!
Appa!
The key you asked for is on this table.
Appa had another son.
His name was Kusumappa Raju.
He meant the world to Appa.
The son brought good fortune with him.
But Kusuma used to behave crazy.
Does he not live here anymore?
Let me finish.
I don't know what happened that day.
he drowned in our estate pond and died.
- Oh, my!
- Yes.
Having lost his beloved son,
Appa lost his mind.
Renuka ma'am stopped
coming out of her room.
- Did you see I left a key on that table?
- Yes.
It's the key to Kusuma's room.
I wonder why he asked
for it after all these years.
Ma'am.
I don't know why, but Appa
asked for Kusuma's room key.
I gave it to him,
afraid he'd make a scene.
I'm informing you just to be safe.
She just won't listen!
Hey! Who is it?! Huh?!
Who is it?
Hey, Kusuma.
You figured I'm in your room, didn't you?
Spying on me in my own house, eh?
BHUVANA'S ESTATE
Jangayya?
Who is that woman?
I don't know, Appa. Never seen her before.
Excuse me?
May I know who you are?
I'm Mr. Siddappa's new nurse.
Dr. Achari sent me.
Achari sir didn't want to give
you bad news right off the bat.
So he told me not to say
anything till you got home.
Siddappa sir is bedridden and in a coma.
Achari sir whispered in his ears that…
you're married, and you're
visiting with your wife soon.
But you showed up alone.
Hello?
There is a long way to go. Get in.
Hey, you.
I was minding my way.
You stopped me to ask who I
was, and I answered out of courtesy.
Shouldn't you tell me who you
are before asking me to hop in?
I'm Mr. Siddappa's son.
Oho! Nice to meet you.
Glad to meet you too. And your name?
I'm--
Why did you stop?
Oh, oh, okay.
I'm sorry. I get it.
My name is Ramappa.
And you are?
Now, that's courteous. I'm Renuka.
Renuka.
Now that formalities are out of the way,
will you get in the car now?
Now, I don't mind.
Dad!
What is it, Ramappa?
Happy birthday, Dad.
Thank you, Ramappa.
Here is your birthday gift.
- What is this?
- It's a poem I wrote for you.
Go on. Read it for me.
O father!
I do not fear the dark,
so long as your smile stays by me.
They praise my unmatched wisdom,
yet never see you behind me.
The world I saw from your shoulders,
I haven't learned to see any other way.
Just because you did not nurse me,
must I not call you Mother?
Is it not my sorrow to live in a language
too poor to understand what I feel?
Be the star that guides my ship,
and lead this little child of
yours, safe across the waters.
Ramappa!
Don't move, you'll get cut.
Will I get a big mustache like you?
You'll get an even better mustache.
Dad!
When did you last see your father?
- It's been five years.
- I could tell.
Wake up, Your Highness.
The sun is out.
Good morning, Appa.
Achchamma!
Good morning!
How come I didn't see you yesterday?
My late brother-in-law has a son, Appa.
Two days ago,
he decapitated my son.
Yes, Appa.
In a fit of rage,
my husband stormed out to kill him.
The nephew.
Instead, the nephew
burned my husband alive!
What?!
Did no one stop him?
What were you doing?
No one stopped them.
Instead, they cheered.
But now that I think about it,
I wasn't even in the dream.
- Dream?
- Yes, Appa.
I was frightened by that dream.
So, although I knew you were coming,
I went to seek help from
the saint in Thurakapalle.
Enough of your stories!
You start making things
up first thing in the morning.
They're not stories.
I am telling it like it is.
Yeah, yeah.
Go, get me a glass of ginger milk.
You never believe anything I say.
I'll share my worries
with Appa once you leave.
Should I get you anything, Appa?
Black coffee.
Black coffee?
Sure, Appa.
Crazy woman.
If you turn her stories into films,
you'll make millions.
Okay, look at me.
Good. Open your mouth
and show your tongue.
- Why?
- Do it, I'll tell you.
I'm a doctor, right?
I don't need to ask how you are.
I can see for myself.
You are doing good.
Hiding the truth even at this age,
are you?
Oh! This is about your dad?
I'll tell you. But first, get out of bed.
You told him I was married?
I'll tell you. Go freshen up first.
We'll talk about it over a coffee.
The new nurse who came
to care for Siddappa sir.
Her name is Renuka.
Shall we ask her if she knows?
Yes. We can.
Achchamma?
Yes. How do you know?
Everyone was saying that…
the house wasn't the same
without Achchamma.
When I saw that the house was glowing,
I knew you were back.
You're a smart lady!
Thank you.
Since you're in charge of the house,
they didn't even bother giving me a room.
Could you arrange a room for me, madam?
I will.
But do you know how to make dark coffee?
- Dark coffee?
- Yes, dark coffee.
- Oh! Black coffee?
- Yes, black coffee!
- Of course, I know!
- Then come with me.
Here, this coffee is made with cow milk.
This one is made with buffalo milk.
This one has goat milk.
And this one has donkey milk.
No matter what milk I use,
the coffee just won't turn black.
Girl, why are you laughing like that?
Nothing. I'll tell you how.
But you need to get me a nice room.
Hey, silly, I'll treat you
like a queen. Just help me.
Hey, be respectful. Don't call me silly.
I'll treat you like a queen, madam.
Please help me.
Fine. Do you have the decoction?
What color does milk turn
when you add decoction?
I guess, a shade of yellow.
What if we use water instead of milk?
There will be no change in color.
It'll remain black.
Is milk the only way to get color?
Isn't black a color in itself?
With hot water, it'll be hot.
And with sugar, it'll also be sweet.
Simple. Black coffee is ready.
When you renounced wealth
and family like Gautama Buddha,
the lack of an heir to
carry on the Bhuvana line…
has affected him a lot.
Look, it's been six months.
It's called a hemorrhagic stroke.
We tried a lot of medications.
Nothing helped.
As a final resort, we even told him
you were married.
Maybe it would've worked
if it were true.
What?
Are you trying to guilt-trip
me over his condition?
Why so harsh? Why would I do that?
Have a seat.
If I had the chance,
I would try to make you
understand one thing, Ramudu.
What is it?
Your dad shows no signs of improvement.
There are many around you,
waiting for him to die,
so they could steal this estate.
For as long as he was alive,
my dad waited to hand over things to you.
Now that responsibility
hangs over my head.
As long as he was alive?
What happened to your father?
It's been eight months.
How?
Almost the same situation.
My wife and I had three children,
all daughters.
"I need a grandson.
Try again," my father said.
My wife couldn't.
And so she got sterilized.
The pain of having no heir killed him.
Even in the sixties,
people are so obsessed over
caste, lineage, religion, and color.
Not just the sixties.
This will go on even in 2020.
And not just in this country.
It's the same situation
all around the world.
We're only different in appearance.
Deep down, all humans are alike.
The world will heal
when people get this.
That is impossible.
Because all humans share a mental flaw.
We look at what is visible to us
and believe that's the truth.
Just as we believe the sun rises
in the east and sets in the west.
The truth is,
the day man started to walk
on his two feet
and migrated to various places,
the human race became one mixed pot.
But we divide ourselves as black or white,
tall or short, fat or thin,
Muslim or Christian.
You're a Kshatriya, and I'm a Brahman.
And that is all people see.
Caste also matters, you say?
Of course.
Which is why I wear my holy thread
and you wear your turban.
You said exactly what I wanted to hear.
You know which nerve to hit, don't you?
Each disease needs its own cure, right?
I'm a doctor. Old habits die hard.
They claimed democracy 20 years ago.
What do you say about that?
Remember, only what I want to hear.
What democracy?
As long as we glorify the
tales of Kings to children,
this country won't be a democracy.
Don't include me in this.
- I'm different.
- Oh, no.
No one is different.
It's just that you're not
socially conditioned yet.
That is it.
Once that happens,
you can finally become one of us.
- Good morning, doctor.
- Good morning.
She's Renuka.
An Anglo Indian.
She was born and raised
in an orphanage.
She's a nurse at my hospital.
We've already been introduced, doctor.
Here.
This is for you.
Why are you serving us?
Where's Achchamma?
Achchamma is way too busy.
She said the doctor was here.
So I thought I'd bring these and meet him.
- Thank you.
- How do you like it here, Renuka?
It's great, doctor.
This house.
The trees that surround it.
I feel like settling here.
I knew you would like it.
Are you recording Mr. Siddappa's vitals?
I am, doctor.
Everything is normal.
But his blood pressure is quite high.
For a person in a coma,
it is rare to have blood
pressure this high.
Okay.
I'll come and check.
Let me see your palm.
- What for?
- I'll tell you. Just show me once.
Your right palm.
Ah! See that lifeline?
It's short from all that cigar smoking.
I don't have such habits.
Look at mine. It reaches my index finger.
Hey, Renuka!
- What's this?
- Hold on.
She's right.
Hey Achari, show me your hand.
Oh please.
Why are you playing along?
Show me.
She's right.
His line is long too.
But see my line.
It's short. But it's thick.
Which means…
I will live multiple lives in one.
Look at yours.
They start out thick but end up thin.
Meaning, your lives…
Yeah! Let me see yours.
Yes, doctor.
You called for me?
Yeah.
What was all that?
Know your place.
Is it wrong to be myself, doctor?
There's no need to be
yourself with everyone.
You'd do well to know your place.
I sent you here because you were
being too playful at the hospital.
Try to be in your limits.
Let's go.
He couldn't say that respectfully?
I'll be myself.
If they don't like me, it's their problem.
THE SONG OF MY LAND
What song is this, Dad?
You keep playing it.
Your mother lives in this song, Ramappa.
That's why I keep playing it.
It's the song I dedicate to my Vasudha.
Just as a golden Bougainville creeper,
she lured me.
She's the young woman of the ages.
I adore your eyes.
Like a star in the sky,
she moves like a bright streak.
As I look at her face,
confusions arise within.
I, a wanderer, who's
always on the move,
take command and lock me up
with those eyes,
my love.
I can never leave,
even if you ask.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I'm going to the town.
Would you like to join me?
Sorry, I don't feel up to it today.
Oh no, what's wrong?
- Is everything alright?
- Yeah.
- It's a bit personal.
- Oh.
- Take care.
- Thank you.
Hey!
Girl!
That's a wild horse.
It can't be controlled.
I'll get you another.
So what if it's wild?
It'll have to be tamed at some point.
Girl! Girl!
Careful!
Oh no! Oh!
I told you.
Look, you hurt yourself!
Don't we hurt ourselves
while learning to ride a bicycle?
This is the same.
I'll deal with you later.
I was searching for something.
I understand what I need now.
I struggle with loneliness.
I understood what
that desperation was.
- That's what I said.
- I stand by you,
I totally lost track of time.
I need to give him saline.
my manhood found its purpose.
The moment your fragrance hits me,
my pride bowed down.
Any warrior
will become a slave
when he looks at her face,
confusions arise within.
I, a wanderer, who's
always on the move,
take command and lock me up
with those eyes,
my love.
I can never leave,
even if you ask.
Hey! There's a pond in your estate?
That pond is very dear to my parents.
My mother died giving birth to me.
Ever since, my father
has come here in her memory.
Your father loves
you and your mother a lot.
How do you know?
Mr. Ramappa! Mr. Ramappa!
What happened?
Nothing.
Okay, shall we go to the pond?
Woah! The pond? Why?
I'm quite fond of water.
I just want to feel what it's
like to stand in the middle of it.
Then, you go ahead.
I'll stay right here.
Why so? Why won't you come?
Well…
I'm afraid of water.
Really? You're afraid of water?
Why are you laughing?
Because I'm afraid of water?
Why?
Aren't men allowed to have fears?
I didn't mean that.
- What's your name?
- Ramappa.
No, your full name.
Bhuvanam Ramappa Rao Bahadur.
You know what Rao Bahadur means, right?
Rao Bahadur is the title
the British gave my grandfather.
We've all carried that name ever since.
We humans are so strange, aren't we?
People name their children not knowing
who they'll grow up to be.
'Rao' means prince.
And 'Bahadur' means brave.
'Rao Bahadur' means 'a brave prince'.
And look at you, afraid
to step into the water.
Fine, you stay here, and I'll go.
Mr. Ramappa!
The world seems so beautiful from here!
There's bliss in these babbling waters!
This wind makes me feel as though
my soul flew out of my
body and spoke to me.
Now I understand why this place
meant so much to your parents.
O you charming beauty,
as my heart looks at you,
peace hits me
like a wave.
- Hello.
- I want to show you a secret. Come.
Come on in.
Do you see that hand?
I do.
Come with me.
Let's check again in half an hour.
Okay.
Now look!
Yeah, it…
- What?!
- See? Isn't it interesting?
Put it back.
Let me see it again.
- Let's go. We'll be back.
- No, no, no.
I want to see it happen.
It doesn't work that way.
I've tried many times.
We'll have to leave the room.
Wait, don't pull.
It's back!
Exactly! It's the secret of
the home of the Bhuvanas.
How's it even possible?
I'll tell you. Come.
Look at your ancestors' paintings.
They all have their
right hand on their chest.
I've read the histories of many kings.
They all do it as a mark of pride.
There, look.
All of them put their hand on their chest.
That's why, even in a coma,
he didn't lose this habit.
They say once pride takes hold,
it lasts till death.
No, no. Don't get me wrong.
It's just a saying.
You've been all over the world.
But you haven't noticed
what runs in your family.
Appa?
Appa!
Achchamma?
What are you doing here?
Wasn't Renuka here?
What is this, Appa?
You've been chanting
her name for a month.
Why would she still be here?
She left right after your father died.
Yeah.
She left, didn't she?
Yes?
I need to have a word with you.
About what?
Not here. In private.
Okay, where shall we talk then?
I'll miss this pond a lot.
So, what is it you wanted to say?
I never thought
I'd come back to this home.
But I did.
Maybe it was just to meet you.
I've never had the desire to marry.
But since I met you…
and spent all this time with you,
I had a change of heart.
I like you.
If you like me too,
I'd like to marry you.
Oh no.
If I led you on,
I'm really sorry.
I never had such feelings for you.
Also, I'm in love with someone else.
So,
it's a no.
Water.
Water! Water!
Water!
- Water! Water!
- What happened?
Water! Water!
I want to leave!
I want to get to the shore!
- Mr. Ramappa!
- Shore!
We're almost there. Don't worry.
I want to get to the shore!
Appa?
Appa!
- Why do you drift off these days, Appa?
- What is it?
Everything's set for
your journey tomorrow.
Mr. Achari will send a taxi by 9 AM.
Taxi?
What happened to our cars?
There are no drivers available.
Where did they all go?
Your father passed away.
Now, you're leaving too.
There is no work here.
So, they're looking for new Masters.
Ramappa!
What was so pressing up here?
You passed away
before getting him married.
I wasn't dying to be here.
I went through hell for 5 years
before getting here.
Enough!
He talks as if only he went through hell
and all of us went up to heaven.
Raising a kid won't cut it!
You need to condition him with our norms.
And you?
Please don't involve me in this.
Were you even listening?
He's leaving tomorrow!
Who will take my lineage forward?
There we go. He's up.
Ask him yourself.
- Who are you all?
- It's us, Ramappa.
Your ancestors.
The ones from the paintings
all around this house.
Don't you recognize us?
Why are you here?
It's nothing, my great
great great grandson.
They say the crop thins
as the herd grows.
But in my clan, it's the weak seeds
that made the herd decline.
So?
We heard you left home when your father
asked you to marry and have children.
- The world is my home.
- Shut up!
To hell with the world!
Army of heirs!
Yes grandpa!
His brain is completely muddled.
Wash his brain and condition it
with societal norms.
Bring him along!
The greatest of grandfathers is here.
To rectify his fate.
Obey me and
Place your head here, o grandson!
Woah! Grandpa, it looks very fresh.
Just like a caveman.
Begin!
I will enter the brain.
I will wreak havoc.
I will wash and clean it up.
I will scramble it.
I will chase the demon away.
I will inject ancestral ego
into your veins.
I will remind you of our pride.
Conditioning. Conditioning.
I will pour my rules all over.
Learn your stature, o prince.
Sit on the throne,
rule without any doubt.
Twist your mustache.
Conditioning.
Show your rage.
Power is a boon.
It was showered on you.
You must change your ways.
All your obstacles must be removed.
By hook or by crook,
I will fill you with the knowledge
of a thousand years.
Without any distractions
or forgetting traditions,
I will teach you the
ways of the kings.
So you won't compare
the good and the bad,
I shall mask your mind.
So the righteous truth
never reaches you,
I shall suffocate
you with intoxication.
Your idea of everyone being equal,
I shall wash it away tonight.
"What is mine, is only mine."
I shall fill it in every
inch of your body.
You are a king of all the land.
The people are slaves.
No one compares to you.
Do not forget this truth.
Wear this ancestral
pride on your head.
I will obey your norms.
Conditioning. Conditioning.
I will be the best of the best men.
I now know my stature.
I will sit on the throne and
rule without a doubt.
I will twist my mustache.
Conditioning.
- I will show my rage.
- Conditioning.
Protect this knowledge as an asset.
Tend to it as a legacy.
For your lineage to continue.
Conditioning.
Forever!
Appa must be here.
Come quickly.
How do I look, Achchamma?
You look like a king, Appa.
'Like a King'?
I am the king!
Can you drive a big car?
Excuse me! Who are you, sir?
Open your mouth.
Ramudu?
What's with the costume?
It's not a costume. It's a royal identity.
Royalty is in my blood.
You won't get it.
- Where's Renuka?
- Renuka?
Why?
Call her in. I have some work with her.
Renuka is not here anymore.
DR. NARAYANACHARI
I fired her.
You fired her? Why?
Because she refused
to follow instructions.
That's why.
But why do you want her now?
- I want to marry her.
- What?
Am I hearing this right?
How can you marry her?
Why? What's wrong in it?
How does her stature compare to yours?
As a clerk's son who
married into wealth…
and built a hospital
on dowry money,
this talk of stature is
quite rich coming from you.
Stature is for men.
Leave women out of it.
They can just focus on femininity.
Ramudu?
Is it really you?
What happened to you?
Head split open, brain washed,
polished, and stitched with gold thread.
Woah, a lot has happened.
Anyway, I don't have
time to chat with you.
I need to produce heirs.
I want you to find her and
convince her to marry me.
If you don't…
People will lose their minds
trying to learn whose son is who.
I…
I've been very delusional lately.
I didn't take Achari seriously.
I need to see that doctor immediately.
Why did you call for me so early again?
A lot has happened, sir.
Where is Lavana?
Lavana sir is down with a fever.
Fever?
What happened?
Appa's madness has gotten worse, sir.
- He's been wreaking havoc all week.
- What happened?
What can I tell you, sir?
What do you mean?
- You said he wreaked havoc.
- Yeah, just listen.
The day after your last visit,
I gave him Kusuma's room key,
as he asked.
Kusuma's room key? Why?
I had no idea then.
But after a while,
he locked Renuka ma'am in that room,
and stormed around the house, shouting.
What are you saying?
She stepped out?
For the first time in…
eight years.
It was me who protected her from Appa.
Is this the havoc you spoke of?
That's not even the half of it.
Here's the worst part.
He got black magic
performed at Kusuma's grave.
- Is this another story or…
- This isn't a story, sir.
It's the truth.
I'm telling you like I saw it.
Get back to work. Go.
He won't believe me.
He never believed me.
Let him go in.
Appa will scare the daylights out of him,
and then he'll believe me.
No, no, no.
What you said is not right, Gandhi.
Why only poor men?
They're not the only ones
contributing to overpopulation.
You think we rich men are any better?
We sowed our seeds everywhere, didn't we?
What does a poor man know anyway?
He's just a soldier waiting to die.
It was kings who stole kingdoms
and screwed queens.
And yet,
you tortured and castrated the poor
to curb the population.
Did it change anything, Mr ?
The population grew so much
no son could tell who his father was.
Anyway, Mr.
can a mistake be rectified
by killing the culprit?
We need to find the
root cause of the problem.
And what is that, tell me?
Oh my!
How did you become a leader
with no basic awareness?
Lack of awareness is
the root cause of the problem.
You must spread awareness if you can.
You can't just go
around sterilizing people.
Why are you making me spell this out?
Achari?
When did you come?
It's been a while.
You were in an important meeting, so…
To hell with your modesty.
Come, I'll introduce you.
Mr.
He's my friend, Dr. Achari.
Say hi to this great man.
- Is he Mr. ?
- Yes. Our very own Mr.
Namaste, sir.
Never thought I'd meet the man
who brought us freedom.
Freedom?
What freedom?
I mean, he brought us independence, no?
Oh, silly! He's not the one
who brought us freedom.
He's that person who took away
the poor man's freedom.
Oh!
So, he's San--
The person you said brought us freedom.
But not freedom of speech.
Don't say it out loud.
Someone could hear you.
Yes, you're right! It's him.
Didn't you recognize him?
I would've, if I could see him.
You can't see him?
It's been 10 years since
he died in our world.
He died?
How?
Well.
Some say he flew a plane
wearing Kolhapuri sandals.
Some say other things.
But the world believes
it was a plane crash.
Why don't you ask him yourself?
Ask whom?
Uh, Mr. Fill-in-the-blank Gandhi.
How can I ask him?
You said he's dead.
And it is personal to me.
Can't just ask anyone. Take this.
What for?
"Liquid Courage", as you call it.
- Yeah, but why now?
- Just drink it.
Chug, chug, chug!
Why do I need courage now?
Well…
To know the truth, of course!
You said we could run the tests…
if we had something from his body, right?
There are some things there.
Go take them.
Ramudu!
What have you done, man?
I know I didn't invite you to
the ceremony we had last week.
Sorry, man.
Please don't mind.
Dad?
Dad!
Who are you?
It's me, Dad. Kusuma.
Kusuma?
- Didn't you die?
- I died in my world, Dad.
But you're not letting
me leave your world.
Go, son. Go, go.
Don't come close!
- Don't touch me!
- Dad, wait!
Dad, wait!
Wait, Dad!
Dad, stop!
- Don't touch me!
- Fine.
I won't touch you. Don't be scared, dad.
You think I'm scared?
Why are you even here?
I'm here to help you, dad.
You're not even the size
of my little finger.
How can you help me?
I might not be as big as your finger.
I know my little finger's nail is
as good as gold to you.
I couldn't bear to see your struggle.
- So, I'm here to help.
- Really?
You need something
from my body, don't you?
Yes, I searched your whole
room and found nothing.
I know exactly how to
get you what you need.
Is it?
Kiddo! Kiddo!
Please show me some grace and tell me.
I'll be reborn as your son.
No, no. Lord knows who your father is.
Tell me, and I'll build you a
tomb with Makrana marble.
Deal. Come along.
I said, don't touch me!
I thought you wanted my help.
Will you really build me a marble tomb?
- Once I give my word--
- Yeah, yeah. Got it. Let's go.
Why did you bring me here?
I'll tell you.
First, answer my question.
Who is that?
That's my great-great-great-grandfather.
The founding father of my dynasty.
And, how is this guy related to me?
What do you mean by "this guy"?
His Highness…
is in no way related to you.
He's my great-great-great-grandfather.
Then, who's that?
He's my grandfather.
How is this guy…
I mean, His Highness, related to me?
What is His Highness to me?
Nothing! He's my grandfather.
So, he's not related to me either?
Then, who's that?
He's my father.
- How--
- He's nothing to you. Stop asking.
Fine, I won't ask. Chill.
Now, who is she?
She's my mother.
She died giving birth to me.
Calm down, Dad. Calm down.
I know how it feels
to lose your loved ones.
Don't cry. Calm down.
And who's this guy?
Up here!
That's the question that haunts me.
You offered to help, right?
Why are you grilling me like this?
What's the rush?
Come close. I'll tell you something.
- What is it?
- You were right.
None of them are related to me.
Isn't this what you wanted to know?
Now make peace with me and come.
We can both hang on the wall.
Oh sure! You're some big official.
The President has
approved your statement.
And I'm supposed to believe
you like a thumb-sucking child?
Quit the bullshit and tell
me where to find your things.
- One last question
- No! No more questions.
- Tell me or I'll figure it out myself.
- Dad, wait, wait.
If you answer this question,
it's a straight road to my things.
One last question.
What is it that everyone
on this wall has that I don't?
- Our royal blood.
- Nonsense.
You'll never change.
Fine, as long as I'm here,
the mystery will keep bugging you.
I'm leaving. You think of the answer.
If you get the answer,
you'll find what you want.
Hey, wait!
Kusuma! Tell the answer and go. Hey!
You're from such a great dynasty.
If such a low-born reveals the answer,
isn't it shameful to your dynasty?
That's true.
I'll find the answer.
- You go.
- Fine. Bye, dad.
I'll smack you if you call me that again.
Sir! Lavana sir!
Your father is crying.
Dad?
Lavana, you're here!
What happened, dad?
Why are you crying?
Don't cry, dad.
Oh, Lavana!
Last night, Kusuma showed up in my dream.
Achchamma, where are you going?
I wondered why he was crying.
It's just about Kusuma.
I'll get back to my work.
You deal with him.
Hey, Achchamma!
Don't cry, Dad.
- Don't cry, Dad.
- Lavana…
Fine, how is Kusuma?
He's crying too.
Why? What's bothering him?
The royal turban.
Turban?
- What do you mean?
- Hey, Lavana.
What do we do when
someone in our dynasty dies?
When someone dies?
If married, we cremate them.
If not, we bury them.
Not that! Don't we
adorn the dead with a turban
and send them off in a royal procession?
Yeah, so?
That's why your little
brother is distressed.
He said, "The whole town gossiped
as I had no procession."
"You sent me off without
a royal turban."
My poor child cried all night.
We must place the turban on him.
Make the arrangements.
What are you saying, Dad?
He died eight years ago.
How can we honor him now?
What if he's dead?
He's still in our backyard.
Have the workers dig up his grave.
Stop it. Your madness has gone too far.
Do you hear yourself?
He's your little brother, Lavana.
Isn't it your duty to
fulfill his last wish?
Yes! I would've done whatever
he wanted if he were alive.
But I can't indulge your
delusions and do as you say.
- Stop dreaming such nonsense.
- La…
- Have a drink and go to sleep.
- Lavana! Wait.
I knew it.
You always envied him.
That's why you always lashed out at him.
My poor child.
He must have gone through hell.
He died when your abuse
became unbearable for him.
And now, you refuse
to fulfill his last wish.
You're the reason.
You're the reason my son is dead.
You think I can't do this without you?
Open the door.
So, what if you refuse?
I'll dig my son's grave
and grant his last wish
with a beautiful turban.
Open the door!
Open the damn door, Lavana!
The job is done.
Just ask “Who's there?"
Won't the 5 senses answer to you?
At the sound of my name,
won't the waves bow down?
Our glow is
ancestral.
Time won't change
our origins.
Our tale is eternal.
There is no mistake or mishap
that you can escape.
I will reveal your secrets.
I will pull your strings.
I will ruffle up the bushes.
All 4 directions will bow down.
The land will flourish as you walk.
If you raise your eyebrows,
the trembling
universe will be visible.
You are me, I am you.
Right, daddy dearest?
It's you in my walk and talk.
My eyes and nose,
all of it resembles
you, daddy dearest.
If you look at me with love,
you can see yourself in me.
Look at me closely,
every inch resembles
you, daddy dearest.
Can you tell milk and water apart?
Why relate this swan to a crow?
How are you related to this tree?
It isn't enough to be
a sapling under its shade.
A weed in the garden.
There's something
wrong with your math.
I will detangle all the
knots in your head.
I will reveal which plant
this seed belongs to.
I will squeeze the
sap out of the roots.
I will bring evidence of the truth.
You cannot escape.
I will reveal your secrets.
I will pull your strings.
I will ruffle up the bushes.
All 4 directions will bow down.
The land will flourish as you walk.
If you raise your eyebrows,
the trembling
universe will be visible.
What is this madness, sir?
It's my karma.
My child!
Oh my!
Look at what you've become.
He used to shine like a black berry.
Look at him now, so white and pale.
Pass that, please.
My child.
You little rascal!
You crawl to my room
from down here, isn't it?
Wait! You'll pay for this!
My son!
Sir, you called for me?
You tried to steal these pumpkins, right?
But sir…
I put them back when my
mother-in-law reprimanded me.
Do you want them now?
Take him away!
Not one or two,
I brought you three things.
These will do, right?
What are you waiting for?
Take them and begin the tests.
Ramudu!
What's this?
I said it casually.
But you've gone too far. It's unjust.
Unjust?
Injustice and immorality
are not in my blood.
You think he just gave them to me?
Come, I'll show you.
There, look!
Look!
Shah Jahan's wife's tomb,
the Taj Mahal, built with
the same Makrana marble.
Look!
Not even his own father
would've done this for him.
Don't you believe me?
Many great monuments are
made of Makrana marble.
The Moti Masjid in Pakistan.
The Victoria Memorial we
visited in Brahmanda Nagaram.
That's Makrana marble too.
And recently, in Dubai--
Shut up, you lunatic!
You go from one obsession to another!
Why are you like this, man?
Ramudu.
Achari.
Can liver cancer cause jaw pain?
How are liver and jaw related?
- There's no such thing.
- Right?
I have a sudden pain in my jaw.
I was worried it was
due to my liver cancer.
Anyway, take those and get the test done.
Do you even hear yourself?
Do you think this is black magic?
You hand over some bones and
find out if he's your son?
Since you asked, I
looked into the process.
DNA testing is no child's play.
The police and lawyers must be involved.
Unless there's a crime,
the court won't let the
police run such tests.
So, listen to me and let this go.
Now I see
why you slapped me for
digging up the grave.
I suspected many people.
But I never thought you,
my childhood best friend,
would stab me in the back.
Hey, Ramudu!
What are you saying?
I can understand.
Digging up his son's
grave without asking
would anger any father.
Your anger is justified.
Hey, this is unfair, man.
Don't say that.
It's my fault. It's all my fault.
Trusting you was my biggest fault.
But, but,
but, but…
How…
Hit me! Go ahead and hit me!
You're afraid I'll know
the truth if we run the test.
That's why you refuse to do it, right?
Not enough.
I know!
If we run the test,
the doubt around his
birth will be cleared.
And it will prove that your
blood runs in his veins.
Still not enough.
I know you're still here.
Why did you run off?
That's why they say
the truth is a hard pill to swallow.
If I'm really deluded,
show me the truth.
If what I believe is false,
Show me!
Ramudu!
- Stay away from my father!
- Hey…
- Don't touch him.
- I need to check on him.
I know what happened.
I know everything.
Dad?
His organs are failing one by one.
His heart is barely moving.
Probably two days.
Take him home and
let him sleep in his royal attire.
Call all your relatives.
Let him die a king's
death in his own court.
Why in this battlefield?
What happened?
Nothing yet.
I'll take care of him. You can go.
BHUVANA'S ESTATE
Who are you looking for, sir?
Bhuvanam Ramappa Rao Bahadur.
Is he here?
Let me call his son.
What's this?
This?
Ramappa sir's father killed
a huge crocodile with a single bullet.
This is its head.
We kept it as a souvenir.
So, the people here have
a habit of killing, huh?
Is Mr. Ramappa into killing too?
Initially, not at all.
It all started after his father died.
I have a doubt.
If this crocodile had killed your master,
would you display his head here?
As a souvenir?
Wait here, sir.
I'll go get his son.
- This is?
- His son.
I am Mr. Ramappa's son.
- The elder son?
- Yes.
Nice meeting you.
You have a younger brother, don't you?
Had.
Come here, ma'am.
- What's your name?
- Achchamma, sir.
Achchamma, just go back down.
There's a man in the jeep I came in.
Bring him here.
Will he be alone, sir?
- I can't recognize him, right?
- Good question.
He's a very dark-skinned
man in his forties.
- Look for that. You'll find him.
- Okay.
What happened, Lavana?
He wants to talk to my father.
- But you interfered.
- Talk to your father?
What happened, sir?
Sorry. May I ask who you are?
I am Dr. Narayanachari.
Ramappa's close friend and well-wisher.
Okay, please sit.
So…
I need to interrogate Mr. Ramappa once.
- Interrogate?
About what, Inspector?
I'll tell you.
Ramappa sir's second son.
Kusumappa?
Yes, Kusumappa.
Claiming he wasn't Mr. Ramappa's son,
a man told me his wife sold their
two-month-old without his knowledge…
to Mr. Ramappa for 100 rupees.
And that sometime ago,
Mr. Ramappa killed that child.
These were that man's exact words.
What?
Yes.
- But my father
- Shush.
See, Inspector.
This guy seems desperate
to squeeze out money.
Kusuma is our Ramappa's son.
None of those things happened.
- And I am a witness to that.
- Yes, Inspector.
My father didn't kill Kusuma.
He fell into the pond
and died before my eyes.
Yes.
So, half the case you made is a lie.
What? Half of it is a lie?
Kusuma is not my father's son.
I've doubted it ever since
I was a child.
What are you saying Lavana?
- Have you gone mad?
- No.
My father went mad thanks to Kusuma.
- And now, he's on his deathbed.
- Shut up, Lavana.
Don't speak ill of the dead
without knowing the truth.
Doctor.
Let him speak.
I will decide what's true and what's not.
Please speak, Lavana.
Why did you suspect at such a young age
that your brother was
not your father's son?
If you saw how my father's
behavior changed after he was born,
anyone would…
feel the same.
Oh, grandson! How
did you turn out so dark?
I'm afraid my lips would
turn black if I kissed you.
Did I say something wrong?
Mom?
Will he turn fairer once he's scrubbed?
One scrub won't do it, son.
We'll give him a scrub every day.
It's going to be alright
"Calm down, little one"
Let's wipe that darkness off your skin
Aren't you daddy's dearest, my darling?
Your dad is hurting, do you see?
This is the second chapter of my story.
Hey, Ramudu.
Hey!
Hey, Ramudu!
Go on.
Thank you.
- What's up?
- Take a look at this.
The government has granted
permission for your biscuit factory.
Turns out Kusuma is lucky for you.
Dear…
He has turned six now.
Shall we send him to school?
Why does he need to
step out of the palace?
You're educated, right?
You homeschool him.
Lavana, come have your lunch.
Not now, Mom.
I'll have it later.
I'll slap you if you talk back to me!
Now move!
A turnover of 20 crores in six years.
These are the fruits of our labor.
On this occasion,
let's rebrand our company.
Let's put a picture of a healthy boy
on our biscuit packet.
What do you think?
Hard work can only get you so far.
Luck plays a major role too.
Ever since Kusuma was born,
luck hasn't left your side, Ramudu.
So, Kusuma's picture would be perfect.
Show me your strength, Lavanappa.
Perfect.
Now, flex both your arms, Lavanappa.
Fantastic!
Go get changed,
then we'll take more photos.
Listen.
Could you take a photo of him too?
One minute, Dad.
I'll be right back.
- Hey, Kusuma, what is it?
- Brother…
Hey! What are you doing, Kusuma?
Brother, let me wear this once.
Ready.
Stand properly.
Hey!
I said stand properly!
Dad?
Lavana.
- How are you?
- I'm fine, Dad.
What did you get me from London?
- What's England's national sport?
- Cricket.
So you got a cricket kit.
Wow!
Cricket kit!
- Thank you, Dad!
- Get me a World Cup.
Dad?
- What?
- Did you get anything for me?
You're just a kid.
What can I get you from London?
Take Lavana's old discarded toys.
Let's go.
Here's the last bite. Open up.
Enough for me, Mom. Feed him.
Does it hurt? Huh?
I'm not yelling to save face.
Imagine how hurt I am.
Brother?
Why is Dad hitting Mom like that?
You really want to know?
You're not Dad's son, right?
That's why he's hitting her.
Hey!
Get off me!
What…
Leave me!
Get off me!
Kusuma, get off me!
Kusuma!
Get off!
- Why did you bite him?
- He said I'm not your son.
Yes, he's right.
Who were you born to?
Happy Birthday, my prince!
How old did I turn, Mom?
Eleven.
How many years to go?
Mom, I'm hungry.
Ten minutes, my prince.
Kesari (sweet dish) will be ready.
Sir! Sir! You'll get a tummy-ache
if you don't remove the seeds.
I'm hungry.
Sir, wait, I'll get the seeds out.
Look, ma'am, he's not listening to me.
He doesn't listen to
anyone when he's hungry.
Kusuma, give me the ball.
Brother? Can I play too?
Cricket isn't for kids.
Go play with my old toys.
Lavanappa, bring him down!
In a pit,
a baby crow was cast away.
Showing no affection,
the dad grows distant.
What was the baby crow's
fault?
Why such hatred
in his father?
Some suspicion
turned into a raging demon.
Is it a parasite?
Did it make us distant?
Did the father not hear
his kid weeping?
Did it leave this nest as
no eye looked its way?
Dad! Dad!
Kusuma! Come, Dad!
- What happened?
- Come, Dad.
Step aside!
Move!
The kid is drowning!
Help!
Someone please help!
Hurry up! Come on!
Hurry!
What was the baby crow's
fault?
Why such hatred
in his father?
My prince!
Some suspicion
- My prince?
- Some suspicion
- My prince!
- turned into a raging demon
Is it a parasite?
- My prince!
- Did it make us distant?
Did the father not hear
his kid weeping?
Did it leave this nest as
no eye looked its way?
Call sir to pour soil on him.
I have nothing to do with this.
It's entirely his fault.
- His fault.
- Ramudu…
His fault.
What's wrong?
They're calling you to pour soil on him.
Let's go.
I have…
nothing to do with this.
This is entirely your fault.
Not mine.
I didn't…
It's not my fault.
It's his fault.
Ask them to plant it there.
Unable to bear my father's torture,
My mother bottled up
her grief over Kusuma's passing.
Tormented by whether
his doubts were valid,
my father spiraled into madness.
Over the years,
I've gotten used to all this.
Wait!
But according to the complaint I received,
Mr. Ramappa bought the kid from
that man's wife for 100 rupees.
But you say he suspected
Kusuma wasn't his son…
and tortured your mother.
The two stories don't match.
I don't understand it either.
If the baby was bought,
why would my father torment my mother?
Suppose the complaint
you got is fabricated.
Then my father's doubts remain.
Look, Inspector,
these doubts drove my father crazy
and got him bedridden.
Even if he dies,
I need to know who's responsible.
Was Kusuma born to
this guy or to my father?
- Or some other--
- Hey!
Your father tortured us all this time.
And now, you?
Inspector, Ramappa is on death bed.
I don't think he's in a
position to talk to you.
And another thing,
Kusuma wasn't bought from anyone.
He was born in my hospital,
in front of Ramappa's eyes.
He is his very own child.
People will tell you a
hundred things, Inspector.
You don't have to take them seriously.
- How dare you?
- Keep talking, and I'll tear you apart.
- What will you do?
- Stay away!
Sir?
Come.
Is it him, sir?
Yes, that's him. Come, sit.
He is Michael. The man who filed the case.
Tell us what happened, Michael.
Inspector, wait a minute.
- Achchamma?
- Yes?
- Get back to work.
- It's fine, sir. My work is done.
Is that so? Then go
attend to Ramudu. Go on.
- Appa is resting fine.
- Go!
Lavana sir!
Achchamma, what happened?
Where's Dad?
Ap… Appa…
Lavana!
Achari!
Achchamma!
Where have you guys
been these past three days?
Hello! Nice to meet you!
Bhuvanam Ramappa Rao Bahadur.
- And you?
- I'm Inspector Jagannadhan.
- Jagannadhan?
- Yes.
Good.
And who is he?
Why are you crying, Mr. Ramappa?
That poor father's grief
is putting me to tears.
So, you then agree that Michael
is Kusuma's father?
What if I say yes?
What if I say no?
Good question.
If you agree that Michael
is Kusuma's father,
since he filed a case that
you killed his son,
we'll take it to court.
If it's proven that you killed Kusuma,
you'd get life imprisonment or
a death sentence. That's it.
- And if I don't agree?
- If you don't?
My investigation will continue.
We'll have the court
authorize an exhumation,
recover the kid's body, and run DNA tests,
thus determining the biological father.
You'll be cleared if you're
proven to be the father.
But if proven otherwise,
things will get complicated.
And, no matter who the father is,
if we find that you killed the boy,
you will be jailed.
Oh?
Then, I don't agree.
What do you mean?
I mean Kusuma is my own son.
My heir. My blood.
Why would I agree that
someone else is the father?
I will cooperate with any investigation.
Wait a minute.
So, Mr. Ramappa?
Will you now agree that
Kusuma is not your son?
Show me your palm.
You need samples, right?
Kusuma's tooth.
If that's not enough,
take a look at this.
Kusuma's little finger.
If that's not enough either,
I have more.
Kusuma's rib.
Why do you have these?
We held a ceremony for Kusuma last week.
I plucked these out as souvenirs.
Do you not believe me? They're original.
Here, smell them.
That way.
Sorry, I'm a vegetarian.
When you shoved the finger
into my nose out of nowhere,
I got nauseous.
Since we have no evidence
that these are Kusumappa's samples,
we will follow protocol and
come with our forensic team,
dig up the grave, and take samples.
Oh, no! Why dig it up, Inspector?
I've prepared a path.
Let me show you.
Move aside!
Look! There's that tree, and
right under it is the grave.
See that door beside it, on the ground.
That door will lead
you straight to Kusuma.
I felt there would be a need for--
Oh…
I mean,
I designed it to visit him
whenever I missed him.
You see, Mr. Lavana,
as your father is mentally unstable,
it's difficult to say whether
he's lying or not.
So, this case seems to be getting bigger.
What did my father even tell you?
Do you really want to know?
He claimed that Kusuma is his own son…
and said they share the same blood.
By the way, Dr. Achari,
when I asked your friend why
he keeps falling unconscious,
He said, "That's just how I am".
"Sometimes, I enter into a
meditative state. Like Jesus."
Make sure nothing like this
happens until the case is closed.
It won't happen, Inspector.
He won't sleep or let others
sleep until this case is closed.
Sorry, uncle.
I got furious
and insulted you for no reason.
It's alright, Lavana.
If the case proves that
Kusuma was born to my father,
it's fine.
It's also fine if it's proved that
he was born to that man.
But if neither of them
turns out to be his father…
Let's go check on my father.
Hasn't the grave been dug yet?
Not there. It's here.
See this door?
It leads straight to the kid's body.
How strange!
Never seen anything like it.
- Right, Senior?
- Yes, Junior.
I haven't either.
This is nothing. There are far
stranger things inside the house.
This is just a pinch of salt.
Did you get all the samples you need?
Yes. But they seem to have
over-watered this tree.
- Testing might be a bit tricky.
- No. Please don't say that.
- All hell will break loose.
- Don't worry, Inspector.
We said it was tricky, not impossible.
Since they didn't use
salt water, it's alright.
Right, Senior?
I was going to say that.
But he panicked before I could, Junior.
So, when can we expect the reports?
- Two weeks?
- Two weeks.
- That's it. Two weeks.
We'll submit the reports in court.
Good. Let's go.
Two more weeks.
Appa?
Get up, I brought food.
Lavana sir!
Appa!
He's stuck like this.
Hey, I'm telling you the truth.
See for yourself, come.
Hello, Mr. Chidambaram?
Look, Dr. Achari.
When you said he got up and
started drinking again,
I considered quitting my practice.
But continued due to
pressure from my family.
I don't think I have enough
medical knowledge to diagnose him.
So, it is better to see
some senior doctor.
See, we still have to diagnose
his mental disorder.
This is a rare symptom of
some psychological disorders.
The victim remains motionless for hours.
But five days? It's weird.
It's better we give him some fluid foods
till he becomes normal.
Only two more weeks.
Two weeks.
The judge has arrived.
Check if Michael is inside.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Mr. Ramappa!
You seem to be glowing!
I just came out of my meditative sleep.
That's the reason behind this glow.
Please share the secret.
We'll follow it too.
It can't be taught.
Then?
It's a superpower you gain
when life goes to shits.
That's so funny.
No.
- I'm serious.
- Ramudu!
I was so worried about you.
Is the job done?
All set.
Let's go.
Let's find the truth.
Ramudu!
You can't enter the court with a turban.
It must be something sketchy
if I was asked to come here in the dark.
The result may or may not prove
Kusuma as Ramappa's son.
But it definitely won't
say Michael is the dad.
How are you so sure?
Because I was the one
who sent Michael to you.
- What?
- Yes.
This test is the only
way to clear my name.
And for that, I need a police case.
- So, I sent Michael-
- You sent Michael to file a fake case.
I got it.
Trust me, I got it.
This is for you to spare Michael.
Having considered the evidence
and arguments of both parties,
the court finds no conspiracy behind
Kusumappa Raju's death
and declares it a suicide.
The court will now disclose
the DNA test results.
Firstly, the probability of paternity…
in the DNA report of
Mr. Michael Sahayam is 0%.
Next, the probability of paternity…
in the DNA report of
Mr. Bhuvanam Ramappa Rao Bahadur
is 99.9%.
Hence, the court declares Mr. Rao
Bahadur as the biological father of…
deceased child Kusumappa Raju,
as established by the DNA results.
Lawyer!
Yes, Mr. Ramappa?
I have my doubts about this judge.
I won't believe it unless
I see the report myself.
Alright.
Mr. Ramappa, the judge
wants the document back.
Please fulfill my last wish and
free me from the curse of this jar.
Ma'am, Appa is no more.
Ma'am!
Relatives and friends, may go one by one,
say three times his name in his ear,
and tell him anything one wants,
for the last time.
Dear,
please forgive me.
I've kept a secret from you.
La…
Lavana…
is not your son.
Ramudu,
I may have kept a lot of secrets from you.
But I genuinely wanted
to tell you this for so long.
I just couldn't.
Forgive me.
You…
you are not your father's son.
I have some good news for you.
That's great. Who's the father?
Renuka!
Don't say no, Renuka.
He's hell-bent on marrying you.
His father's death has
disturbed him mentally.
This marriage might
help him recover from it.
There's a truth you must know.
Forget it.
We all have our own set of truths.
One's truth is nobody else's business.
I won't ask you anything.
You don't tell me either.
But the truth is--
There we go again!
You don't have to reveal any truths.
Okay. I'll think about
it and let you know.
Give it a good thought.
He's definitely not the
gentleman you knew before.
I lost both my wife and child
at childbirth.
Now they torment me with questions about
who will carry the lineage forward!
Why don't you marry again?
There's no room in my heart
for anyone but Vasudha.
So, what are you planning to do?
I'm thinking of adopting a kid.
Sadly, she died at childbirth.
I'll announce that
only the child survived…
and introduce him
to the world as my heir.
- How much did it cost?
- Hundred rupees.
Here. Don't ask where I got him from.
He is my gift to the Bhuvana Dynasty.
BHUVANA'S ESTATE
I'm telling you, move away!
Get out of my way!
Is this today's item?
Let's chuck it out.
Oh!
Sandalwood!
It's an expensive death.
Big man has died with his eyes open.
Hey!
Is this arrogance
because you're sandalwood?
Again?!
The arrogance isn't coming
from this piece of wood.
It's coming from this piece of wood.
I'll set it right.
Careful! He's a royal.
Royal, huh?
Come back in a bit to collect
the ashes and gold.